The greatest zombie cast ever disassembled.
The Dead Don't Die is a comedy, horror film directed by Jim Jarmusch.
In the sleepy town of Centerville, the lives of a number of
interconnected characters are disrupted by the undead.
Chief Cliff Robertson, played by Bill Murray.
Officer Ronnie Peterson, played by Adam Driver.
Officer Mindy Morrison, played by Chloë Sevigny.
Zelda Winston, played by Tilda Swinton.
Bobby Wiggins, played by Caleb Landry Jones.
Hermit Bob, played by Tom Waits.
The Dead Don't Die is a 2019 American absurdist zombie comedy and
metacinematic film written and directed by Jim Jarmusch.
It features an ensemble cast including Bill Murray, Adam Driver, Chloë Sevigny, Steve Buscemi, Tilda Swinton, Tom Waits, Danny Glover, Caleb Landry Jones, Rosie
Perez, Iggy Pop, Carol Kane, RZA, Austin Butler, and Selena Gomez and follows a small town's police force as they combat a sudden zombie invasion.
The film had its world premiere as the opening film at
the Cannes Film Festival on May 14, 2019.
It was released in theaters in North America on June 14, 2019 by Focus
Features, and earned $15.3 million at the box office.
It received mixed reviews from critics.
The film explores themes of hermit, small town,
pennsylvania, usa, cemetery, breaking the fourth wall.
The tone is lighthearted and dark.